prestigeconstructions.com 2014-03-28

# Prestige

Privacy Policy

##### This policy was last modified on 1st January 2014.

##### Statutory Message

The information found on this website is conceptual and not a legal offering. The promoter reserves the right to change, alter, add or delete any of the specifications mentioned herein without prior permission or notice.

##### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When filling out a form on our site, for any of the above-mentioned reasons, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

READ MORE 

##### What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer)
  * To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from us, simply respond to the email received letting us know the same & we will have you taken off from our database.

##### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information.

##### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser [if you allow] that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

READ MORE 

##### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##### Third-party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

##### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

##### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.prestigeconstructions.com/terms.php>.

READ MORE 

##### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date at the top of this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

##### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

The Falcon House,  
No. 1, Main Guard Cross Road  
Bangalore, Karnataka 560001  
India  
+91 80 25591080 

##### Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our Privacy Policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

  * Federal Trade Commission's Fair
  * California Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Privacy Alliance
  * Trust Guard Privacy Requirements
